export default {
  title: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
  syllables: [
    {
      question: '벼',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅂ'
    },
    {
      question: '뼈',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅃ'
    },{
      question: '펴',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅍ'
    },
{
      question: '배',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅂ'
    },
{
      question: '빼',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅃ'
    },
 {
      question: '패',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅍ'
    },
  {
      question: '불',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅂ'
    },
  {
      question: '뿔',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅃ'
    },
    {
      question: '풀',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅍ'
    },
   {
      question: '발',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅂ'
    },
   {
      question: '빨',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅃ'
    },
{
      question: '팔',
options: "ㅂ ㅃ ㅍ",
      answer: 'ㅍ'
    },
  ]
}
